<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <string-array name="canadianCities">
        <item>Toronto</item>
        <item>Vancouver</item>
        <item>Ottawa</item>
        <item>Montreal</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="canadianCitiesDescription">
        <item>Toronto, the capital of the province of Ontario, is a major Canadian city along Lake Ontario’s northwestern shore. It\'s a dynamic metropolis with a core of soaring skyscrapers, all dwarfed by the iconic, free-standing CN Tower. Toronto also has many green spaces, from the orderly oval of Queen’s Park to 400-acre High Park and its trails, sports facilities and zoo.</item>
        <item>Vancouver, a bustling west coast seaport in British Columbia, is among Canada’s densest, most ethnically diverse cities. A popular filming location, it’s surrounded by mountains, and also has thriving art, theatre and music scenes. Vancouver Art Gallery is known for its works by regional artists, while the Museum of Anthropology houses preeminent First Nations collections.</item>
        <item>Ottawa is Canada’s capital, in the east of southern Ontario, near the city of Montréal and the U.S. border. Sitting on the Ottawa River, it has at its centre Parliament Hill, with grand Victorian architecture and museums such as the National Gallery of Canada, with noted collections of indigenous and other Canadian art. The park-lined Rideau Canal is filled with boats in summer and ice-skaters in winter.</item>
        <item>Montréal is the largest city in Canada\'s Québec province. It’s set on an island in the Saint Lawrence River and named after Mt. Royal, the triple-peaked hill at its heart. Its boroughs, many of which were once independent cities, include neighbourhoods ranging from cobblestoned, French colonial Vieux-Montréal – with the Gothic Revival Notre-Dame Basilica at its centre – to bohemian Plateau.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Toronto"></string>
    <string name="Vancouver"></string>
    <string name="Ottawa"></string>
    <string name="Montreal"></string>
</resources>
